https://www.newagestore.com/about/terms/

Terms of Use, Privacy, Disclaimer and Copyright Policies
The services offered on this site (www.newagestore.com and encompassing http://forums.newagestore.com) are not an exact science, we strongly recommend that you do not take too seriously or literally the interpretations you may receive during a reading on this site. Please use your common sense and own judgement, the site readings are meant to reflect your own thought processes and projections – this does not absolutely predict events or give absolute advice as to what actions you should take or decisions you should make regarding your current life circumstances. In short, NewAgeStore is not responsible for any advice given on the site, this site is for entertainment purposes only.
NewAgeStore makes no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, as to the operation of the site, the information, content, materials or products included on this site. NewAgeStore will not be liable for any damages arising from use of this site. All readings and advice arising from use of this site are understood to be for entertainment purposes only, they do not constitute professional advice.
At NewAgeStore.com we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not disclose your email address. (We promise!!… also we’re well aware of the Karmic effects!)
NewAgeStore.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. NewAgeStore.com does provide accumulative statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics do not include any personally identifying information.
You as our customer and guest are our number one priority and we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on our site to make visiting and/or shopping at NewAgeStore.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience.
Comments made on our site – may be removed or edited at our discretion.
Your consent: By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by NewAgeStore.com. If we make changes to our privacy policy, the information will be posted so that you are always aware of what changes have been made in regard to the information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
NewAgeStore.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: NewAgeStore.com
Copyright unless otherwise mentioned all content and images remains the property of NewAgeStore.com in both this world and the karmic one!
Advertisers: We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Registration Forms: Our site’s registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address).
Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Order Forms (when active): Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and unique identifiers.
Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer’s contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
External Links: This site contains links to other sites. NewAgeStore.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security: This site has security measures in place (when selling product) to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard. It encrypts your most important personal information – your credit card number, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet.
We pride ourselves on our commitment and dedication to all our customers and we assure you of our integrity at all times. We do not and will not release any of your personal information. If you are placing an order, with us directly: To enable us to process your orders we require your name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. We may also use your email address to contact you with important functionality changes to our Web site.
For any further information or concerns please contact us
Choice/Opt-Out: Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us. You can contact us
Data Quality/Access: This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: contact us
Contacting the Web Site: If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us
GDPR
Under the European Union’s General Data Privacy Regulation (‘GDPR’), you may have certain rights pertaining to your personal data. If you are covered by the GDPR, you may contact us in order to exercise any of your data privacy rights. It may take up to 30 calendar days to process each request.
Please be aware that if you exercise your data privacy rights you may lose access to your account(s) and the features found in our Digital Platforms (i.e. websites, mobile applications, etc.). Once an account has been deleted, it cannot be restored.
